[{"answer": "Well Piers TMZ says they are believed to have been taken in Fallujah in 2004.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Brian what can you tell us about these pictures?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Well they've issued statement Commander Bill speaks of the Pentagon Press Office.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "And what is the Defense Department saying about all these?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "It would apply in the case of war crimes but the Pentagon specifically told me earlier today they don't believe that this is a war crime under the Geneva Conventions and under some of the more traditional definitions of war crime.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Does the statute limitations apply in the case of war crimes generally?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well there have been some rare instances of US forces US troops in both Iraq and Afghanistan behaving in ways that are not sanctions by the United States and are contrary to military regulation and uniform and coat of military justice.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "On the assumption that they're genuine images and we haven't independently verified them, what would you're reaction be to American troops behaving in that manner?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Will I -- this is very troubling to me because when I was secretary in 2008 because of various problems in the nuclear force I ended up simultaneously firing the secretary of the Air Force and the chief of staff of the Air Force as a matter of accountability because of mishaps associated with our nuclear capabilities.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "What did you make of that story?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "think it's actually essential.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Is that a good idea do you think?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think it had -- would have any impact on the morale of the troops still fighting there because the reality is the President has made a number of decisions with respect to Afghanistan.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I think it is important for Americans and particularly our men women in uniform to understand the debates that went on in Washington and to humanize and personalize those debates so that they know that these issues were debated seriously, that there was a lot of passion involved that the President asked hard questions.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Is it really a patriotic duty to do this before those two things have happened?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, frankly I don't think any of that is particularly a secret.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Is it good for United States of America, that the Vice President according to the most experience defense chief of the last for four or five decades says he's been wrong about absolutely every foreign policy issue in that entire period?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Benghazi happened after I left office so I'm not familiar with a lot of the details that are associated with it except for what I've been able to read in the newspapers.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "And I would imagine it would put more pressure on Hillary Clinton to try and explain why if that is the case this ever happened?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "American politics including the American Congress have always been very rough and tumble.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Have you in all your time dealing with Washington in Congress, have you ever known it'd be so obstructively divisive to the American national interest?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "You know, when I got -- no, what happened as I got -- first of all, I didn't know I was going to be on then and I was so taken aback.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "What were you trying to say?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Never thought you have to make a speech?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Did you have a couple of alcoholic temples to get in the mood?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "You've been really sober?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Because you're a godmother to Angelina Jolie?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I felt happy that it was over and thrilled to have that Golden Globe in my hand and we walked back into the press room and everything and everybody was very friendly and congratulations I didn't think any of it.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "How did you feel about the speech?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "I mean, that word I said is not a big deal, is it?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Of course you can.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Can I say that?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Oh, I did.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "I mean did you think when you made it you were doing something quite special?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Did you get, you know, Leonardo DiCaprio coming up and saying, \"Hey you were fantastic\" or all the stars?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Much more.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "More than 50?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "It's about 90 something.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Do you know how many it is?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Yeah, I thought 90 projects, yeah at least.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Is it really?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Do I?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, that's a ...", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "And I want to ask you my signature question, how many times Jacqueline Bisset -- have you ever been properly in love?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well it will.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Do you think it will?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I could never see, you know, it's probably because my parents were not happy.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I've been in love every time in my major relationships, I've been in love absolutely.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "How many times have you say you've been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, I've had like five major relationships.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "To how many times?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Give me the five again.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "ORGAN: ... Steve McQueen, Christopher Plum and Dean Martin and Anthony Quinn, if I could plunge you on a desert island for the rest of your days with one of those leading men, who would you take?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "One of the best moments, yeah.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Was winning the globe the best moment of your career?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "It's over.", "docId": "140115pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Is it over already?", "qSentId": 504}]